<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Pages on PonyFest</title>
    <link>https://ponyfest.horse/6.5/pages/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Pages on PonyFest</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://ponyfest.horse/6.5/pages/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://ponyfest.horse/6.5/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ponyfest.horse/6.5/about/</guid>
      <description>About PonyFest Online! Right! We know what you’re thinking: What the hay is PonyFest Online? Where did you come from? This wasn’t a thing a week ago!
You’d be right! PonyFest Online is an online Pony Convention with a one week turnaround - Our entire organization, schedule, everything has been built this week! We were inspired by Ruef’s awesome online Vendor Hall for our friends and family who’ve been directly hurt by the loss of in-person pony conventions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Charity Concert T-Shirt</title>
      <link>https://ponyfest.horse/6.5/shirt/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ponyfest.horse/6.5/shirt/</guid>
      <description>Charity T-Shirt For the PonyFest × PVFM Concert, we have another fantastic concert shirt AND a powerful charity attached!
Our charity this time around is The Trevor Project, the world’s largest suicide prevention and crisis intervention organization for LGBTQ+ youth. Providing free counseling over chat, phone, and text as well as doing important advocacy and activist work, Trevor Project has supported gay, lesbian, bisexual, transgender, non-binary, gender-nonconforming, and questioning young people across the entire United States since 1998.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Guests</title>
      <link>https://ponyfest.horse/6.5/guests/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ponyfest.horse/6.5/guests/</guid>
      <description>GuestsCosmicKeyframe Productions CosmicKeyframe is a jack of all trades! Streamer, artist, animator, VA -- She has had her hand in every aspect of the MLP Community and beyond! Besides her own works, she is also a main team member of famous nerdcore channel DAGames, and an active player in SaltyDKDans Pokemon Friendlocke! DeviantArtTwitterWebsiteYouTube Crackle&amp;#39;s Cousin Cosplay Crackle’s Cousin Cosplay is a master level award winning cosplay troupe. They strive to inspire and to always live by the principles of harmony.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Schedule</title>
      <link>https://ponyfest.horse/6.5/schedule/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ponyfest.horse/6.5/schedule/</guid>
      <description> ScheduleSchedule Loading...</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Staff</title>
      <link>https://ponyfest.horse/6.5/staff/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ponyfest.horse/6.5/staff/</guid>
      <description>Staff Coordination Lycan - Con Chair Reiuiji - Vice Con Chair Events Simul - Lead Luck Rock - Music Lead A/V Larscis - Lead Reiuiji - Staff Gaming Leslie - Lead Tabletop Eliwood Sain - Lead Steel - Staff Design TechyCutie - Lead HauntedTuba - Staff Dawnfire - Bit Rate&amp;rsquo;s Mom Social Media Kevin - Lead Vendors Screw Loose - Lead VIP Relations Sirris - Lead Discord Fizzbuzz - Lead Midnight Aegis - Moderator Phosphorshy - Moderator PFC Rye of Shadows - Watcher King_CreepaLot - Watcher TheMostTopDog - Watcher Lord Midnight - Watcher Rarijack - Watcher Changelings Jamis - Staff Katharine - Staff Dexanth - Staff Charity Perrydotto - Lead Eurostream Jamis - Lead Special Thanks Twilight//RainbowDerpy - Streaming OPS, Resident Pony Town Expert Sleepy - PVFM Owner, Mentor Industrialice - PonyTown Project Lead Programmer PonyTown Team - For being supported for all these years Reiuiji - Our Resident Sylveon PonyTown Server Design Team Twilight//RainbowDerpy Cloudburst Delfynx Onyx Deadshot TheRealDashy </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Vendors</title>
      <link>https://ponyfest.horse/6.5/vendors/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ponyfest.horse/6.5/vendors/</guid>
      <description>VendorsCandled with Care Enjoy the wonderful scents of Equestria with our selection of hand poured pony candles. Each candle features a unique scent featuring some of your favorite characters. Come by and check out our lovely selection of colorful candles!
Twitter&amp;#8203; Corey&amp;#39;s Corner Pillows, plushies, acrylic charms, enamel pins, and facemasks for every geek and fandom from anime to video games and lots of ponies! If you want to cuddle up with a carry along style Luna or wake up with the iconic beginning with Ralof from Skyrim, I have you covered!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
