<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Pages on PonyFest</title>
    <link>https://ponyfest.horse/4.0/pages/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Pages on PonyFest</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://ponyfest.horse/4.0/pages/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://ponyfest.horse/4.0/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ponyfest.horse/4.0/about/</guid>
      <description>About PonyFest Online! Right! We know what you’re thinking: What the hay is PonyFest Online? Where did you come from? This wasn’t a thing a week ago!
You’d be right! PonyFest Online is an online Pony Convention with a one week turnaround - Our entire organization, schedule, everything has been built this week! We were inspired by Ruef’s awesome online Vendor Hall for our friends and family who’ve been directly hurt by the loss of in-person pony conventions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Charity Auction</title>
      <link>https://ponyfest.horse/4.0/auction/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ponyfest.horse/4.0/auction/</guid>
      <description>PonyFest Charity Auction PonyFest Online! 4.0&amp;rsquo;s charity auction benefited NAMI, the National Alliance on Mental Illness.
Disclaimer PONYFEST IS IN NO WAY LIABLE FOR ANY TRANSACTIONS MADE DURING THE AUCTION! PonyFest as a group does not handle the money or auction items in any way, shape or form. The donation of money and the shipping of items is arranged between the specific individuals involved. PonyFest simply facilitates the contact between the parties involved.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Guests</title>
      <link>https://ponyfest.horse/4.0/guests/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ponyfest.horse/4.0/guests/</guid>
      <description>Guests Devyn Dalton (Autographs) Devyn Dalton is a Canadian born actor, dancer, and stunt performer. Strongly recognized for her motion capture performance roles and voice work.She was scouted by an agent in her home town of Edmonton, who recruited her to the film industry in Vancouver, BC. Devyn continued her training in dance and theatre, performing throughout Canada and Worldwide. Some of her accomplishments include landing her first feature film &#34;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Schedule</title>
      <link>https://ponyfest.horse/4.0/schedule/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ponyfest.horse/4.0/schedule/</guid>
      <description> pfoSchedApi = &#39;\/schedule.json&#39;;   Schedule Schedule Loading...  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Staff</title>
      <link>https://ponyfest.horse/4.0/staff/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ponyfest.horse/4.0/staff/</guid>
      <description>Staff  Coordination  Katharine Berry - Princess   Events  Simul - Lead Lycan - Music Lead Foal Papers - Staff   A/V  Larscis - Lead Alex (Coach) - Staff Reiuiji - Staff winter501st - Staff winchester572 - Staff   Gaming  Leslie - Lead   Tabletop  Eliwood Sain - Lead   Design  TechyCutie - Lead Dawnfire - Bit Rate&amp;rsquo;s Mom Amodwithoutamark - Staff Leh - Staff Twisted Sketch - Staff Viwrastupr - Staff   Social Media  Kevin from TrotCon - Lead   Vendors  Ruef - Lead B.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Vendors</title>
      <link>https://ponyfest.horse/4.0/vendors/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ponyfest.horse/4.0/vendors/</guid>
      <description>Vendors Abigail Starling I&amp;#39;m a professional comic illustrator, but in addition to comics I have prints, keychains, buttons, plush, and stationery! I love working in a cute and colorful style, and also offer goods for multiple fandoms in addition to Pony!
DeviantArt&amp;#8203;Instagram&amp;#8203;Ko‑Fi&amp;#8203;Patreon&amp;#8203;Tumblr&amp;#8203;Twitter&amp;#8203;  AfroThunder Heya everyone! AfroThunder here, and ready to button you up! You have a favorite pony/creature/purple-bellied snootfargle*, chances are that I may have a button for you!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>