<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Pages on PonyFest</title><link>https://ponyfest.horse/pages/</link><description>Recent content in Pages on PonyFest</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://ponyfest.horse/pages/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>About</title><link>https://ponyfest.horse/about/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ponyfest.horse/about/</guid><description>About PonyFest Online! Right! We know what you’re thinking: What the hay is PonyFest Online? Where did you come from? This wasn’t a thing a week ago!
You’d be right! PonyFest Online is an online Pony Convention with a one week turnaround - Our entire organization, schedule, everything has been built this week! We were inspired by Ruef’s awesome online Vendor Hall for our friends and family who’ve been directly hurt by the loss of in-person pony conventions.</description></item><item><title>Charity Auction</title><link>https://ponyfest.horse/auction/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ponyfest.horse/auction/</guid><description>PonyFest Charity Auction Disclaimer PONYFEST IS IN NO WAY LIABLE FOR ANY TRANSACTIONS MADE DURING THE AUCTION! PonyFest as a group does not handle the money or auction items in any way, shape or form. The donation of money and the shipping of items is arranged between the specific individuals involved. PonyFest simply facilitates the contact between the parties involved. PonyFest is not able to assist in the case of items being lost, damaged or otherwise impacted in transit.</description></item><item><title>Guests</title><link>https://ponyfest.horse/guests/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ponyfest.horse/guests/</guid><description>Guests Racquel Belmonte Racquel Belmonte is a voice actor, sketch comedian, improviser, and writer living in Vancouver, British Columbia. When she’s not performing in her comedy duo Carmelahhh, she is performing with her all-female comedy troupe Nasty Women, her Blind Tiger Comedy Houseteam Reynolds, a variety of Instant Theatre shows as a Guest Artist, and on her lonesome in other cool comedy shows around the city. She’s performed frequently in the Vancouver International Improv Festival, in the Del Close marathon in New York, at Ryan Stiles’ Upfront Theatre in Bellingham, and most recently at the Toronto Fringe Festival.</description></item><item><title>Schedule</title><link>https://ponyfest.horse/schedule/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ponyfest.horse/schedule/</guid><description> pfoSchedApi = 'https:\/\/schedule-api.ponyfest.horse\/schedule\/'; Schedule Schedule Loading...</description></item><item><title>Staff</title><link>https://ponyfest.horse/staff/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ponyfest.horse/staff/</guid><description>Staff Coordination Dexanth - Princess Katharine Berry - Other Princess Events Simul - Lead Lycan - Music Lead Aphinity - Staff Foal Papers - Staff A/V Larscis - Lead Callum - Staff Ramble - Staff Reiuiji - Staff ServerRat - Staff WaffleThief - Staff winchester572 - Staff IT Taiko - Staff Dani - Staff Gaming Leslie - Lead Adamtheamazing64 - Staff Tabletop B.</description></item><item><title>Vendors</title><link>https://ponyfest.horse/vendors/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ponyfest.horse/vendors/</guid><description>Vendors Abigail Starling I&amp;#39;m a professional comic illustrator, but in addition to comics I have prints, keychains, buttons, and stationery! I love working in a cute and colorful style, and also offer goods for multiple fandoms in addition to Pony!
DeviantArtInstagramKo-FiPatreonTumblrTwitter Alienkitty Designs Cute japanese inspired creations, with a touch of my own flare. I got buttons, stickers, and charms galore!
DeviantArtFacebookTwitter ALOS shop Good day, everypony, long time no see!</description></item></channel></rss>