<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Pages on PonyFest</title><link>https://ponyfest.horse/pages/</link><description>Recent content in Pages on PonyFest</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://ponyfest.horse/pages/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>About</title><link>https://ponyfest.horse/about/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ponyfest.horse/about/</guid><description>About PonyFest Online! Right! We know what you’re thinking: What the hay is PonyFest Online? Where did you come from? This wasn’t a thing a week ago!
You’d be right! PonyFest Online is an online Pony Convention with a one week turnaround - Our entire organization, schedule, everything has been built this week! We were inspired by Ruef’s awesome online Vendor Hall for our friends and family who’ve been directly hurt by the loss of in-person pony conventions.</description></item><item><title>Guests</title><link>https://ponyfest.horse/guests/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ponyfest.horse/guests/</guid><description>Musicians Eurobeat Brony Eurobeat Brony is the earliest and longest-lasting pioneer of brony music. From penning the original "Discord" from which The Living Tombstone's remix was borne, to several other classics of the scene including "Luna", "Diamond Dogs", "Batty", and several lasting remixes of the show, Eurobeat Brony (or Odyssey, or T. Stebbins, or Ken Blast from the Initial D soundtrack…) knows a thing or two about how to string old classics, new hits, and cutting-edge tracks together into an unforgettable performance.</description></item><item><title>Schedule</title><link>https://ponyfest.horse/schedule/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ponyfest.horse/schedule/</guid><description> Schedule Schedule coming soon!</description></item><item><title>Staff</title><link>https://ponyfest.horse/staff/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ponyfest.horse/staff/</guid><description>Staff Coordination Lycan - Event Lead Katharine Berry - Figurehead Princess Music Luck Rock - Staff ExplodingPonyToast - Staff Blackened Blue - Staff A/V Larscis - Lead Design Techycutie - Lead cassettepunk - Staff Social Media Kevin from TrotCon - Lead Discord Fizzbuzz - Lead Gajinka - Assistant Lead Midnight Aegis - Moderator Changelings Jamis - Staff Charity Perrydotto - Lead</description></item></channel></rss>