<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Pages on PonyFest</title><link>https://ponyfest.horse/pages/</link><description>Recent content in Pages on PonyFest</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://ponyfest.horse/pages/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>About</title><link>https://ponyfest.horse/about/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ponyfest.horse/about/</guid><description>About PonyFest Online! Right! We know what you’re thinking: What the hay is PonyFest Online? Where did you come from? This wasn’t a thing a week ago!
You’d be right! PonyFest Online is an online Pony Convention with a one week turnaround - Our entire organization, schedule, everything has been built this week! We were inspired by Ruef’s awesome online Vendor Hall for our friends and family who’ve been directly hurt by the loss of in-person pony conventions.</description></item><item><title>Guests</title><link>https://ponyfest.horse/guests/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ponyfest.horse/guests/</guid><description>Musicians 4EverfreeBrony Hey, I'm Garrison, or 4EverfreeBrony. Been a musician in the fandom for about 7 years now. Love ponies, and I love music. I'd like to thank the guys at PonyFest for putting on this awesome event, and for inviting me to perform. Let's have a great show!
BandcampTwitterYouTube General Mumble BandcampTwitterYouTube BlackIceMusic Producing music since 2014, BlackIceMusic was originally inspired by Martin Garrix on the commercial side and Woodentoaster/Glaze on the fandom side and more recently created a similar sound to his current idol Dirty Palm.</description></item><item><title>Schedule</title><link>https://ponyfest.horse/schedule/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ponyfest.horse/schedule/</guid><description> Schedule Schedule coming soon!</description></item><item><title>Staff</title><link>https://ponyfest.horse/staff/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ponyfest.horse/staff/</guid><description>Staff Coordination Lycan - Event Lead Katharine Berry - Figurehead Princess Music Luck Rock - Staff ExplodingPonyToast - Staff Blackened Blue - Staff A/V Larscis - Lead Design Techycutie - Lead cassettepunk - Staff Social Media Kevin from TrotCon - Lead Discord Fizzbuzz - Lead Gajinka - Assistant Lead Midnight Aegis - Moderator Changelings Jamis - Staff Charity Perrydotto - Lead</description></item></channel></rss>