<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Pages on PonyFest</title><link>https://ponyfest.horse/pages/</link><description>Recent content in Pages on PonyFest</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://ponyfest.horse/pages/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>About</title><link>https://ponyfest.horse/about/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ponyfest.horse/about/</guid><description>About PonyFest Online! Right! We know what you’re thinking: What the hay is PonyFest Online? Where did you come from? This wasn’t a thing a week ago!
You’d be right! PonyFest Online is an online Pony Convention with a one week turnaround - Our entire organization, schedule, everything has been built this week! We were inspired by Ruef’s awesome online Vendor Hall for our friends and family who’ve been directly hurt by the loss of in-person pony conventions.</description></item><item><title>Charity Concert T-Shirt</title><link>https://ponyfest.horse/shirt/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ponyfest.horse/shirt/</guid><description>Charity T-Shirt
#shirt-ad img { border-radius: 10px; max-width: 100%; } For the PonyFest × PVFM Concert, we have another fantastic concert shirt AND a powerful charity attached!
Our charity this time around is The Trevor Project, the world’s largest suicide prevention and crisis intervention organization for LGBTQ+ youth. Providing free counseling over chat, phone, and text as well as doing important advocacy and activist work, Trevor Project has supported gay, lesbian, bisexual, transgender, non-binary, gender-nonconforming, and questioning young people across the entire United States since 1998.</description></item><item><title>Guests</title><link>https://ponyfest.horse/guests/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ponyfest.horse/guests/</guid><description>Musicians AWal AWal hails from the not too far away polar vortex, bringing a sound that is both fast and energetic. Be sure to bring your kandi and glowsticks because his show is definitely not one to miss.
SoundcloudTwitchTwitterYouTube Bolt the Super-Pony When not being consumed by the void, Bolt DJs on PonyvilleFM where his show Music is Timeless (Fridays @ 9 PM PDT) has been introducing Pony fans to great new music and old classics since 2015.</description></item><item><title>Schedule</title><link>https://ponyfest.horse/schedule/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ponyfest.horse/schedule/</guid><description> pfoSchedApi = 'https:\/\/schedule-api.ponyfest.horse\/schedule'; Schedule Schedule Loading...</description></item><item><title>Staff</title><link>https://ponyfest.horse/staff/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ponyfest.horse/staff/</guid><description>Staff Coordination Lycan - Con Chair Events Simul - Lead Luck Rock - Music Lead A/V Larscis - Lead Reiuiji - Staff Gaming Leslie - Lead Tabletop Eliwood Sain - Lead Steel - Staff Design TechyCutie - Lead HauntedTuba - Staff Dawnfire - Bit Rate&amp;rsquo;s Mom Social Media Kevin - Lead Vendors Screw Loose - Lead VIP Relations Sirris - Lead Discord Fizzbuzz - Lead Midnight Aegis - Moderator Phosphorshy - Moderator PFC Rye of Shadows - Watcher King_CreepaLot - Watcher TheMostTopDog - Watcher Lord Midnight - Watcher Rarijack - Watcher Changelings Jamis - Staff Katharine - Staff Dexanth - Staff Charity Perrydotto - Lead Eurostream Jamis - Lead</description></item></channel></rss>